{
  "questions": [{
    "compQuestion": "4 + 5 = ?",
    "answer": 9,
    "display": true
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "2 + 5 = ?",
    "answer": 7,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "3 - 2 = ?",
    "answer": 1,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "6 - 3 = ?",
    "answer": 3,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "4 * 2 = ?",
    "answer": 8,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "10 / 5 = ?",
    "answer": 2 ,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "x + 1 = 4, x = ?",
    "answer": 3,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "2x + 20 = 34, x = ?",
    "answer": 7,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "6x + 8 = 14, x = ?",
    "answer": 1,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "10x + 13 = 103, x = ?",
    "answer": 9,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "3x + 6 = 21, x = ?",
    "answer": 5,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "y = 4x^2, y'' = ?",
    "answer": 8,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "y = 3x^2, y'' = ?",
    "answer": 6,
    "display": false
  }, {
    "compQuestion": "y = 2x^2, y'' = ?",
    "answer": 4,
    "display": false
  }]
}
